Marching to the lowest bar. Thinking
less gets you far. Logic's left behind
the tread. Idiots get to set the end.
Reason drowned by empty noise. Common
sense replaced by boys, blindly led by
liars. Bold, truth gets bought and
cheaply sold. If knowledge is a crime,
then what's the price we pay?
Jumping down is trending now. Ignorance
is what they say. Critical thrown away.
Standing ground to be cliche.
Stupid all the rage.
Hey,
turn of the page.
[Music]
TV screens blast mindless shows. Social
media feeds the flame. Fools get famous
overnight while libraries collect the
dust.
Information at our fingertips.
We choose to stay in the dark.
Celebrating mediocrity
is tearing us apart.
Ding down and trending down.
Critical
thrown away standing ground to be clich.
Hey,
stupid all the rage.
turn on the page.
[Music]